Office of the Boards of Advisors Records UA200
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- International Board of Overseers, 1988 -- 2020; UA200.008; 3.6 Linear Feet; 12 Digital Object(s) Of the 12 digital objects in this series, 1 represents a zip file comprising 4 files and .12 MBs of data.
  - Media Activity Report for Tufts in India, 2005-11-01; UA200.008.009.00003; Boards of Overseers Office
    A second file named 'India Media Report 12-05' was also transferred. Content was identical to this file.
  - Tufts in India Follow-Up Report, 2006-05-01; UA200.008.009.00004; Boards of Overseers Office
    Tufts in India Follow-up Report
  - Report from the International Board of Overseers Meeting; Tufts European Center, Talloires, France, 2006-06-10 -- 2006-06-11; UA200.008.009.00005; Boards of Overseers Office
    Report from the International Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Report from the International Board of Overseers Meeting; Medford, Massachusetts, 2006-11-02 -- 2006-11-03; UA200.008.009.00006; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the International Board Meeting Cabot Intercultural Center - Medford Campus of Tufts University, 2011-10-20; UA200.008.009.00007; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Report from the International Board Meeting Cabot Intercultural Center - Medford Campus of Tufts University
  - International, 2005 -- 2015; UA200.008.023 (Box 23)
  - International, 2013 -- 2015; UA200.008.024 (Box 24)
    Meeting agendas, minutes, and materials, Spring 2013-Spring 2015.
  - International meeting minutes, 2017 -- 2018; UA200.008.00001; 4 Digital Object(s); .12 Megabytes
  - International Board Minutes - India, 2019-01-01; UA200.008.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Kilobytes
  - International Board Minutes - London, 2019-06-01; UA200.008.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 28 Kilobytes
  - Report from the Tufts University International Board of Advisors Meeting, 2020 February 27 -- 2020 February 28; UA200.000750; 32.6 Kilobytes
  - Report from the Tufts University International Board of Advisors Meeting, 2020 June 24; UA200.000751; 26.5 Kilobytes
- Library Board of Overseers, 1985 -- 2000; UA200.009; 2.4 Linear Feet
  This series consists of materials, similar to the "Working Paper" of the Board of Trustees, from Board meetings. This Board was dissolved in 2000.
  - Library Board-Miscellaneous, 1985 -- 2000; UA200.009.002.00082 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Libraries -- Wessell, 1988; UA200.009.002.00083 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
    Bound Report "The University Library" 1981/82 -- 1987/88 by Murray S. Martin, University Librarian, October 1988
  - Libraries -- Membership, 1989; UA200.009.002.00084 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Libraries -- Info Mailings, 1989 -- 1990; UA200.009.002.00085 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Libraries -- Ginn, 1992; UA200.009.002.00086 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Health/Sciences Library, 1989 -- 1990; UA200.009.002.00087 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - University Library Council, 1988 -- 1990; UA200.009.002.00088 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Libraries -- Collection Mgmt., 1985; UA200.009.002.00089 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Libraries -- Construction Project, 1990; UA200.009.003.00001 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Libraries -- Photographs, 1989; UA200.009.003.00002 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
    Includes photographic prints of the Library Board of Overseers Committee Members
  - Library Board of Overseers Mtg. Thursday, April 6, 2000; UA200.009.003.00003 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Library Overseer Meeting Friday, November 5, 1999; UA200.009.003.00004 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - LIBRARY BOARD OF OVERSEERS MTG. Friday, September 17, 1999; UA200.009.003.00005 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Universities Libraries Board Meeting Friday, May 21, 1999; UA200.009.003.00006 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Library Board Meeting 2/12/99, 1999; UA200.009.003.00007 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Library Board Meeting 10/30/98, 1998; UA200.009.003.00008 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Library Overseers Meeting Thurs. & Fri. June 4&5, 1998; UA200.009.003.00009 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Library Mtg. - May 9, 1997; UA200.009.003.00010 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Libraries Board of Overseers Wednesday, October 9, 1996; UA200.009.003.00011 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - LIBRARY OVERSEERS - APRIL 24, 1996; UA200.009.003.00012 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Libraries April 7, 1995; UA200.009.003.00013 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Libraries 11/9/95, UA200.009.003.00014 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Library Mtg - April 20, 1994; UA200.009.003.00015 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Libraries September 21, 1993; UA200.009.003.00016 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - 3/93 libraries, 1993; UA200.009.003.00017 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - LIB 10/92, 1992; UA200.009.003.00018 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - May '92 - libraries, 1992; UA200.009.003.00019 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - library 11-12-91, 1991; UA200.009.003.00020 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Library 4-22-91, 1991; UA200.009.003.00021 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - LIBRARIES MEETING 11/16/90, 1990; UA200.009.003.00022 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Libraries Meeting - April 3, 1990; UA200.009.003.00023 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Libraries Mtg. -- October 26, 1989; UA200.009.003.00024 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Libraries Mtg. -- January 31, 1989; UA200.009.003.00025 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Libraries Mtg. -- December 2, 1987; UA200.009.003.00026 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Arts and Sciences Library User Survey, 1994 -- 1995; UA200.009.003.00027 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
- Medical Board of Overseers, 1988 -- 2020; UA200.010; 2.4 Linear Feet; 22 Digital Object(s) Of the 22 digital objects in this series, 2 represent zip files comprising 5 files and .13 MB of data.
  20 years from date of creation. Open for research.
  - Medical/Sacker Board of Overseers MTG. Wednesday, April 28, 2004; UA200.010.003.00029 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
    Open for research.
  - Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Mtg. Wednesday, October 15, 2003; UA200.010.003.00030 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical/Sackler Board of Overseer Mtg. Wednesday, April 9, 2003; UA200.010.003.00031 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Board of Overseers Meeting Thursday, October 31, 2002; UA200.010.003.00032 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Board of Overseers Meeting Thursday, April 18, 2002; UA200.010.003.00033 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Mtg. Thursday, October 25, 2001; UA200.010.003.00034 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Board of Overseers Meeting Thursday, April 5, 2001; UA200.010.003.00035 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Board of Overseers Meeting Wednesday, October 18, 2000; UA200.010.003.00036 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Board of Overseers Meeting April 6, 2000; UA200.010.003.00037 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Board of Overseers Mtg. Friday, November 5, 1999; UA200.010.003.00038 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical/Sackler Board Meeting Thursday, April 29, 1999; UA200.010.003.00039 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Board Meeting, 1998; UA200.010.003.00040 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Board of Overseers Meeting Thursday, April 30, 1998; UA200.010.003.00041 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Board of Overseers Meeting Thursday, February 5, 1998; UA200.010.003.00042 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Board of Overseers Meeting Thursday, October 30, 1997; UA200.010.003.00043 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Mtg. - April 24, 1997; UA200.010.003.00044 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Overseers Meeting Thursday, February 6, 1997; UA200.010.003.00045 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Board of Overseers Tuesdat, November 19, 1996; UA200.010.003.00046 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Med. Mtg.- May 9, 1996; UA200.010.003.00047 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical - October 16, 1995; UA200.010.003.00048 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical May 23, 1995; UA200.010.003.00049 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Board Mtg. Dec. 1, 1994; UA200.010.003.00050 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - 5/4/94 - Medical, 1994; UA200.010.003.00051 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Feb 2, 1994; UA200.010.003.00052 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Med, 1993; UA200.010.003.00053 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical, 1993; UA200.010.003.00054 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medicine, 1993; UA200.010.003.00055 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical, 1992; UA200.010.003.00056 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical, 1992; UA200.010.003.00057 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical, 1992; UA200.010.003.00058 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical, 1991; UA200.010.003.00059 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical, 1991; UA200.010.003.00060 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical, 1991; UA200.010.003.00061 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Meeting, 1990; UA200.010.003.00062 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Meeting, Aug. 1, 1990; UA200.010.003.00063 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Mtg. -- May 2, 1990; UA200.010.003.00064 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Mtg. -- February 7, 1990; UA200.010.003.00065 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Meeting -- November 1, 1989; UA200.010.003.00066 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Mtg. -- August 2, 1989; UA200.010.003.00067 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Mtg. -- May 3, 1989; UA200.010.003.00068 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Mtg. -- February 1, 1989; UA200.010.003.00069 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Mtg. -- November 2, 1988; UA200.010.003.00070 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Mtg. -- August 3, 1988; UA200.010.003.00071 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Mtg. -- May 4, 1988; UA200.010.003.00072 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Medical Mtg. -- February 3, 1988; UA200.010.003.00073 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Report from the Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Meeting, 2004-04-28; UA200.010.010.00001; Boards of Overseers Office
    2004 Minutes
  - Report from the Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-04-20; UA200.010.010.00002; Boards of Overseers Office
    Report from the Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Executive Session, 2005-04-20; UA200.010.010.00003; Boards of Overseers Office
    Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Executive Session
  - Tufts Global Health Interest Group-Medical Student Presentation, 2005-10-01; UA200.010.010.00004; Boards of Overseers Office
    Tufts Global Health Interest Group-Medical Student Presentation
  - Strategic Plan of the Tufts University School of Medicine, 2006-03-01; UA200.010.010.00005; Boards of Overseers Office
    Strategic Plan of the Tufts University School of Medicine
  - Report from the Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Meeting, 2007-04-19; UA200.010.010.00006; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Meeting, 2007-10-18; UA200.010.010.00007; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Meeting, 2008-04-10; UA200.010.010.00008; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Research Portfolio Review Board of Overseers Summary, 2008-04-10; UA200.010.010.00009; Boards of Overseers Office
    Research Portfolio Review Board of Overseers Summary
  - Cover letter from Dean Rosenblatt, 2008-05-12; UA200.010.010.00010; Boards of Overseers Office
    Cover letter from Dean Rosenblatt
  - Report from the Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Meeting, 2008-10-23; UA200.010.010.00011; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Meeting, 2009-10-22; UA200.010.010.00012; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Meeting, 2009-04-16; UA200.010.010.00013; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Meeting, 2009-04-22; UA200.010.010.00014; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Meeting, 2010-04-15; UA200.010.010.00015; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Meeting, 2010-10-07; UA200.010.010.00016; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Medical/Sackler Board of Overseers Meeting, 2011-10-20; UA200.010.010.00017; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Medical/Sackler, 2005 -- 2015; UA200.010.024 (Box 24)
  - Medical meeting minutes, 2016 -- 2018; UA200.010.00001; 4 Digital Object(s); .1 Megabytes
  - Medical School Board of Advisors Minutes, 2018-10-19, UA200.010.00002; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Medical Board of Advisors Minutes, 2019-05-14; UA200.010.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 29 Kilobytes
  - Report from the Meeting of the Board of Advisors to the School of Medicine, 2019 October 22; UA200.000744; 33 Megabytes
  - Report from the Meeting of the Board of Advisors to the School of Medicine, 2020 May 08; UA200.000752; 35.5 Kilobytes
- Nutrition Board of Overseers, 1990 -- 2019; UA200.011; 3.6 Linear Feet; 19 Digital Object(s) Of the 19 digital objects in this series, 2 represent zip files comprising 5 files and .2 MBs of data.
  - Nutrition Meeting, Oct. 18, 1990; UA200.011.003.00074 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition, 1994; UA200.011.003.00075 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition Overseer Meeting March 8, 1995; UA200.011.003.00076 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition, 1995; UA200.011.003.00077 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition - April 23, 1996; UA200.011.003.00078 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition Mtg. - April 14, 1997; UA200.011.003.00079 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition Board of Overseers Mtg. Tuesday, October 7, 1997; UA200.011.003.00080 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition Board of Overseers Friday, May 8, 1998 CANCELED, UA200.011.003.00081 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition Mtg. - November 9, 1998; UA200.011.003.00082 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition Board Meeting Thursday, May 20, 1999; UA200.011.003.00083 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition Board of Overseers Mtg. Friday, November 5, 1999; UA200.011.003.00084 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition Board of Overseers Meeting Thursday, May 18, 2000; UA200.011.003.00085 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition Board of Overseers Meeting Monday, November 13, 2000; UA200.011.003.00086 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition Board of Overseers Mtg. Thursday, May 17, 2001; UA200.011.003.00087 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition Board of Overseers Meeting Thursday, October 4, 2001; UA200.011.003.00088 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition Board of Overseers Meeting Thursday, April 18, 2002; UA200.011.003.00089 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition Board of Overseers Mtg. Thursday, October 31, 2002; UA200.011.003.00090 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition Board of Overseers Mtg. Tuesday April 8, 2003; UA200.011.003.00091 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Nutrition Board of Overseers Meeting October 29-30, 2003; UA200.011.003.00092 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Friedman Nutrition Board of Overseers Wednesday, October 27, 2004; UA200.011.003.00093 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Friedman Nutrition Board of Overseers Tuesday and Wednesday, May 4-5, 2004; UA200.011.003.00094 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - The Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy, Tufts University Report from the Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-05-03; UA200.011.015.00001; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    The Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy Tufts University Report from the Board of Overseers
  - The Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy, Tufts University Report from the Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-10-25 -- 2005-10-26; UA200.011.015.00002; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Board of Overseers-Strategic Plan Discussion, 2005-10-01; UA200.011.015.00003; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Board of Overseers-Strategic Plan Disussion
  - Campaign Planning Briefing for Friedman School Board of Overseers, 2005-10-25; UA200.011.015.00004; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Campaign Planning Briefing for Friedman School Board of Overseers
  - Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy Presentation by Judith B. Diamond, 2005-10-26; UA200.011.015.00005; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy Presentation by Judith B. Diamond
  - Board of Overseers presentation, 2005-10-01; UA200.011.015.00006; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Board of Overseers presentation
  - The Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy, Report from the Board of Overseers Meeting, 2006-04-25 -- 2006-04-26; UA200.011.015.00007; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Nutrition Board of Overseers Consultation Dinner; Radius, Boston, 2006-04-25; UA200.011.015.00008; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - The Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy, Report from the Board of Overseers Meeting, 2007-04-17; UA200.011.015.00009; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    The Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - The Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy, Report from the Board of Overseers Meeting, 2007-11-13 -- 2007-11-14; UA200.011.015.00010; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    The Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy, Report from the Board of Overseers Meeting
  - The Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy, Report from the Board of Overseers Meeting, 2008-05-06 -- 2008-05-07; UA200.011.015.00011; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - The Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy, Report from the Board of Overseers Meeting, 2008-09-23 -- 2008-09-24; UA200.011.015.00012; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - The Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy, Report from the Board of Overseers Meeting, 2009-05-06 -- 2009-05-07; UA200.011.015.00013; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - The Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy, Report from the Board of Overseers Meeting, 2010-05-10 -- 2010-05-11; UA200.011.015.00014; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - The Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy, Report from the Board of Overseers Meeting, 2011-11-16; UA200.011.015.00015; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Nutrition, 2008 -- 2015; UA200.011.022 (Box 22)
    Meeting agendas, minutes, and materials, Fall 2008-Spring 2015.
  - Nutrition, 2005 -- 2008; UA200.011.023 (Box 23)
    Meeting agendas, minutes, and materials, Spring 2005-Spring 2008.
  - Nutrition meeting minutes, 2016 -- 2018; UA200.011.00001; 4 Digital Object(s); .16 Megabytes
  - Friedman BOA Minutes, 2018-10-17, UA200.011.00002; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Friedman BOA Minutes, 2019-04-02; UA200.011.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 32 Kilobytes
  - Report from the Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy Board of Advisors Meeting, 2019 October 02 -- 2019 October 03; UA200.000743; 38.02 Megabytes
- Veterinary Board of Overseers, 1988 -- 2020; UA200.012; 2.4 Linear Feet; 21 Digital Object(s) Of the 21 digital objects in this series, 2 represent zip files comprising 5 files and .16 MBs of data.
  - Vet. Mtg, October 14, 1988; UA200.012.003.00095 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Vet. Mtg, May 2, 1989; UA200.012.003.00096 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Vet. Mtg, October 30, 1989; UA200.012.003.00097 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Vet. Mtg, May 31, 1990; UA200.012.003.00098 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Meeting, 1990; UA200.012.003.00099 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Vet Mtg, 1991; UA200.012.003.00100 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Vet Mtg., 1991; UA200.012.003.00101 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Vet Mtg., 1992; UA200.012.003.00102 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Vet Mtg., 1992; UA200.012.003.00103 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Vet Mtg., 1993; UA200.012.003.00104 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Mtg. May 17, 1994; UA200.012.003.00105 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Vet Board Mtg. Oct. 26, 1994; UA200.012.003.00106 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary May 11, 1995; UA200.012.003.00107 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary - October 25, 1995; UA200.012.003.00108 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Vet. Mtg. - May 9, 1996; UA200.012.003.00109 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board of Overseers Tuesday, October 29, 1996; UA200.012.003.00110 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Mtg. - May 14, 1997; UA200.012.003.00111 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board Meeting November 12, 1997; UA200.012.003.00112 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board of Overseers Mtg. Friday, April 24, 1998; UA200.012.003.00113 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board Meeting November 16, 1998; UA200.012.003.00114 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board Meeting Thursday, May 6, 1999; UA200.012.003.00115 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board of Overseers Mtg. Friday, November 5, 1999; UA200.012.003.00116 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board of Overseers Mtg. May 11, 2000; UA200.012.003.00117 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting Monday, October 30, 2000; UA200.012.003.00118 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board of Overseers Mtg. Wednesday, April 18, 2001; UA200.012.003.00119 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board of Overseers Mtg. Thursday, October 18, 2001; UA200.012.003.00120 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board of Overseers meeting West Palm, FL March 2-4, 2002; UA200.012.003.00121 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board of Overseers Mtg. Thursday, May 9, 2002; UA200.012.003.00122 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting Thursday, October 10, 2002; UA200.012.003.00123 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board of Overseers Mtg. Wednesday, April 23, 2003; UA200.012.003.00124 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board of Overseers Mtg. Saturday, November 1, 2003; UA200.012.003.00125 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board of Overseers Mtg. Monday, May 24, 2004; UA200.012.003.00126 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board - Special Meeting w/ President Bacow - October 5, 2004; UA200.012.003.00127 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Veterinary Board of Overseers Mtg. Tuesday, October 26, 2004; UA200.012.003.00128 (Box UA200 Shared 4)
  - Report from the Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-05-05; UA200.012.016.00001; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Report fromt he Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Executive Session Report from the Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-05-05; UA200.012.016.00002; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Executive Session Report from the Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Report from the Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-10-28; UA200.012.016.00003; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Report from the Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Executive Session Report from the Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-10-28; UA200.012.016.00004; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Cummings Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting, 2006-05-03; UA200.012.016.00005; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Report from the Cummings Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Report from the Cummings Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting, 2006-10-27; UA200.012.016.00006; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Cummings Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting, 2007-05-09; UA200.012.016.00007; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Cummings Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting, 2007-10-23; UA200.012.016.00008; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Cummings Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting, 2008-04-30; UA200.012.016.00009; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Beyond Boundaries FY 2008, 2008-07-11; UA200.012.016.00010; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Beyond Boundaries FY 2008
  - Follow up to Overseers Meeting of April 30, 2008 memo, 2008-05-28; UA200.012.016.00011; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Follow up to Overseers Meeting of April 30, 2008 memo
  - Report from the Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine Board of Overseers Meeting, 2008-10-21; UA200.012.016.00012; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Report from the Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine Board of Overseers Meeting